dnainfo.com 2013-04-25

# Privacy Policy - About Us - DNAinfo.com New York

DNAinfo ("

 _DNA_

") is committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy will advise   
you about how DNA protects your personal information and about what choices you   
have concerning the use of that information.  Please read this policy carefully.  
The Information DNA Collects and How DNA Uses It  
When you visit this site (the "

 _Site_

"), you may be invited to provide personal information in  
order to receive additional information and services. This information may include your  
name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, and other information.

The Site generally collects personally identifying information only with your specific   
knowledge and consent so that we may send you information about DNA or our carefully  
selected affiliates. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a  
survey, subscribe to our email(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are  
asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number.  
Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you  
visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the   
operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and your Internet  
Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which  
you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your  
university.

**Information Shared With Third Parties**  
In addition, DNA may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to  
perform functions on its behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, and analyzing  
data.  These DNA agents have access to personal information needed to perform their  
functions, but may not use it for other purposes.  Except as provided in this Privacy  
Policy, DNA keeps all of your personal information private and will not share it with any   
third party unless, you have authorized DNA to do so or DNA is legally required to do  
so.  DNA may also release personal information when it believes, in good faith,  
that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply the provisions of its  
[Terms of Use](http://www.dnainfo.com/new-york/about-us/terms) or to protect the rights, property or safety of DNA, its users, or others.

DNA retains the right to transfer your personal information to a successor in interest  
pursuant to a change of control of DNA or a sale of all or substantially all of DNA’s  
assets.

**Security of Your information**  
The Site has security measures in place intended to protect against the loss, misuse,  
and alteration of the information under DNA’s control.  DNA uses industry standard  
encryption to help ensure that all the personal information you provide is encrypted and  
remains private.  This helps to maintain the confidentiality of your information.  DNA  
strives to protect your personal information, however, DNA cannot ensure or warrant the  
security of any information you transmit to DNA.

**Cookies**  
DNA may use cookies to improve your experience at the Site. Cookies are small pieces  
of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping  
purposes.  The cookies DNA uses in and of themselves do not personally identify users,  
although they do identify a user’s computer as well as the first name of the person  
logging in DNA may use cookies to remember information users give to DNA so they  
don’t have to reenter it each time they visit the Site.  You are always free to decline the  
cookies if your browser permits.  Even without a cookie, you will still be able to use most  
of the features on the Site.

**Children Under the Age of 16**  
DNA does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children  
under 16 years of age.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By visiting the Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the collection  
and use of this information by DNA.  DNA will always fully disclose its privacy policies,  
and will promptly post any changes to its policy on this page.

You agree that DNA may retain and use your personal information as described in this  
Privacy Policy until you inform DNA that you do not agree with this Privacy Policy and  
agree that you will not use the Site for a reasonable time thereafter.  By using the Site  
after DNA posts any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes.

If you choose to visit DNA, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this  
Privacy Policy and DNA [Terms of Use](http://www.dnainfo.com/new-york/about-us/terms).

**Applicable Law**  
This Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the  
State of New York, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law.  You agree that  
any action at law or in equity that arises out of or relates to any use of the Site will be  
filed only in the state or federal courts located in New York County and you hereby  
consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of  
litigating any such action.

**Contacting the Site**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the  
Site, the content available on the Site or your interactions with the Site, you can contact:

DNAinfo  
1414 Avenue of the Americas  
11th Floor  
New York, NY 10019
